轰动本市的婴儿失踪案
The city is shocked by missing baby cases.
到目前为止 三个月内已经增至18名
Eighteen babies were taken in the past three months.
警方仍然未有任何突破性发现
The police have made no breakthrough
束手无策
and the investigations have reached the bottleneck.
本台记者经警务署长…
-The Commissioner of Police… -All my clients have good lives.
一下子便到了！请停车
Here we are. Stop!
我跳
I'm coming!
有点麻烦
Something is wrong.
中招了
Damn it.
不管那么多了
Forget it.
小心小心
Be careful.
看…极具格调的建筑
Look! It's a stylish building!
请进内参观一下
Let's take a look inside.
两位请跟我过来
This way, please.
这一幢屋格调幽雅
This way. This house is elegant
保管一千米内了无人烟
and there is no one else here within 1 km.
开车去买菜 车程只要五分钟
It's only a five-minute ride to the market.
这么多优点 总会有些缺点吧
This house can't be that perfect. Surely there must be some defects.
当然有点点缺点的
There is a little defect,
但影响不大
but it won't be a problem.
跟我来
This way.
这房子的缺点便是…
The defect is that
没什么装修
it's not really renovated.
这叫做没什么装修？
You call this as not really renovated?
没事的 结构没事
The structure is fine.
只不过一场小小的火灾
There was just a little fire.
老婆
-Honey. -Hush.
给你看点东西
I'll show you something.
鸟语花香
Nature!
保证你们越住越喜欢
You'll love this place in no time.
你觉得怎样？
What do you think?
去！早叫那无良业主
Damn it. I've asked the owner
把房子修葺好才拿出来卖
to renovate the house first.
徒浪费我的时间
What a waste of time!
我运气好
How lucky!
现在那个笨蛋会买这个房子呢？
Who the hell would buy it now?
气死我
Damn it!
走吧…
Let's go.
别动
Don't move!
老公呀！买下吧 我喜欢这房子
Dear, let's buy it.
它很有性格
I like it.
性格？
It has character.
是吗？
Character?
你知道我喜欢我们的房子是怎样的
-Really? -You know how I like it.
我知道
I know.
那就 先下点订金吧
Pay the deposit first then.
别吵
Quiet!
偷车？自己搞定
Did you try to steal my car? Put this on yourself.
是…我自己搞定
Okay, I'll put it on myself.
真厉害
Incredible!
当然啦！我老公是个警察哩
Of course. My husband is a policeman.
快吧
Keep walking.
我在走呀
Aren't I walking now?
至今天为止
Up until today,
这两个月有18名婴儿失踪
18 babies went missing in the past two months.
由犯案手法看来 是同一人做的
They seem like the work of one person.
到目前为止 所有失踪婴儿家人
None of the missing babies' families
都没收到任何勒索信
has received any blackmail letters so far.
亦没任何政治或恐怖组织
Nor has any political or terrorist group
承认是他们干的
claimed responsibility.
局长 这案件离奇古怪
Chief, this is bizarre.
你认为我们应否与女飞侠联络呢
Shall we approach Wonder Woman?
虽然好几次她也主动来帮我们
Even though she helped us before,
但我们连她是什么人也不知道
we still don't know who she is.
根本没办法去联络她
We can't reach her at all.
由失踪的均是男婴这点看来
All missing babies are boys.
我相信他们并不是有什么勒索要求
This shows that it's not blackmailing.
喂…
Hey…
可能是与邪教有关系
Maybe it has something to do with cults.
见到有人在会议室冲出来吗？
Did anyone rush out of the conference room?
没有
No.
局长
Chief!
（下一个将会是你的儿子）
跟我来
Come with me.
婴儿房在楼上 那边是手术室
The babies' ward is upstairs. Operation rooms are over there.
我好担心我们的儿子呀！
I'm worried about our son.
我们不如立刻把他带回家吧！
Let's take him home now.
阿刘
Lau!
儿子今早才出世 如果现在带回去
He was just born this morning.
医生说不负责的
The doctor won't take the risk if we discharge him now.
阿刘…
Lau--
算了！留下吧
Fine! We'll leave him here.
既然如此 为何不叫女飞侠来帮忙？
Why didn't you call Wonder Woman for help?
局长太太 我也没办法找到她
Ma'am, we have no way to contact her.
况且我已多派了很多人手
I've sent more men here.
如果有事
Staying here
那婴儿在家或医院也没分别
is just as safe as staying at home.
快点看着我老婆
Take care of her!
是 局长
Okay.
局长 刘Sir 南区刚有辆巴士失事
Chief, Officer Lau, there's a bus crash in the Southern District just now.
院长说可能要用这一边的病床
The warden might need these beds,
叫我们商量一下
so we need to think about it.
阿刘你先出去
Lau. You may leave first.
阿刘他们的目标只是对付我儿子
Lau. It's my son that they are after.
你说可不可以用别的…
How about we find someone
换一换呢？
to swap with my son?
找谁的儿子？
Whose son?
那确是很缺德的…
I guess that's immoral.
况且他们要抓的是你儿子
They want your son.
你怎么换 他们也找到的
They will find him eventually.
是…如果被人知道…很难为情
Yes, it'd be embarrassing if others knew.
无论如何也要撑一去
Let's brace ourselves.
撑…
Brace ourselves.…
局长太太 对不起
I'm sorry, ma'am.
刘Sir吩咐没他命令
Officer Lau said no one can enter
任何人不能进去
without his permission.
算了
Forget it! Look up there!
什么事？
What's wrong?
有婴儿掉下来呀
The babies are falling down!
接住他们！接住他们
-Catch them! -Catch them!
我的儿子呀
-My son! -My son!
接住儿子呀
Catch our son!
那个才是我们的儿子呀？
Which one is our son?
随便一个吧
Either one of them can be him!
那个才是呀？
Which one?
女飞侠呀
Wonder Woman!
女飞侠啊
-Wonder Woman! -Wonder Woman!
下来了
She's coming down!
她的血留在上面 你拿去化验吧
There's some blood on the wall. Run some tests on it.
不是我们的
This is not our baby. This is not our baby!
对！是个女的
It's a girl!
女的？是我的女儿呀
-A girl? It's my daughter! -Hey!
没事就好了！吓死我了…
I'm so glad you are fine. -I was so scared. -This is bad.
找人上去把血抹掉拿去化验
Get someone to collect the blood sample.
是 刘Sir！跟我来
-Yes, sir. Come with me. -Okay.
东东 医院里又有个婴儿失踪了
-Hello? -Tung-tung, another baby is missing.
我有很多事要做 要很夜才回来
I'll be back late tonight.
好的
Okay.
你不开心？
Are you upset?
不是！你用心办事吧
No. Work hard tonight. -Goodbye. -Goodbye.
这么喜欢打！下次把你的头都劈下来
You always like to fight. I'll chop off your head next time.
快守着门口
Guard the door!
公公 你要的童子 我已带回来了
Master, here is the baby boy you want.
你替我把十九阿哥抱进去
Take the 19th prince inside
跟其他皇阿哥一起休息
to rest with the other princes.
是 公公
Yes, Master.
阿三
Sum.
你的心跳得太快了
Your heart is beating too fast.
我没有
No, it's not.
你是不需要有记忆
Memories do you no good,
更不可以有感情
neither do feelings or emotions.
我没有
I don't have any.
等下一个黄道吉日到来
I'll wait for the next auspicious day.
我会在他们当中
Among all the babies,
选一个做皇帝
I'll choose one to be the emperor.
中国是不可以没皇帝的
China must have an emperor.
一就是你自己爬上来
一就是你掉下去！没有人可以帮到你
Either you climb up by yourself or you will fall! No one can help you.
爬吧！
Climb up!
青青 爬吧！爬呀
Ching-ching, climb up!
不要掉下去 爬吧
Don't fall! Climb!
你又做梦了？
Did you have a nightmare again?
我可不可以进来？
May I come in?
仪器开动了
I'm working.
你知我不想有人进来影响我
You know I don't want anyone to disturb me.
这几年 我每晚都梦见那件隐形衣
I've been dreaming of the invisible robe every night for years.
昨晚我还见到它在阳光下隐形了
Last night, I dreamt that it was finally completed.
那衣服是否一直锁在保险库？
Has it always been kept in the safe?
是！有什么事吗？
Yes, why?
没有 警方今天打电话来
The police called today
问我人怎样才可隐形 叫我发表意见
and asked me how one can be invisible.
在隐形衣未完成之前
Before the invisible robe is finished,
你是不想让人知道的
you don't want others to know about it.
就算完成了 我也不想被人知道
Even if it's finished, I want to keep it a secret forever
因为这类发明
because an invention like this
好容易被人利用来作战争武器的
may easily be used as a war weapon.
那么你研究这隐形衣
Then why are you still working on it?
对你有什么意义？
What does it mean to you?
当我专心去研究一样东西时
I feel the happiest
就是我最开心的时候
when I'm glued to my work.
你不怕我偷了那隐形衣？
Don't you worry that I'd steal it?
不怕
No.
一个人怎会偷自己的东西呢？
You can't steal what's already yours.
要不要咖啡？
Do you want some coffee?
好呀
Yes, please.
小姐呀 你给我那十八个童子的
Miss, the dates of birth
生辰八字…
of those 18 babies…
是否有关联的？
Are they related in any way?
奇怪了
It's strange.
他们个个都是紫微入宫 左辅右弼
They all have a royal destiny.
全部都是皇帝命啊
They are all fated to be emperors!
皇帝？
Emperors?
谁人会抓那么多属皇帝命的孩子呢？
Why would anyone kidnap so many little emperors?
妹妹
My sister!
是不是想吃？想吃便过来吧
Do you want some? Come over then.
来！来
Come. Come.
你跟我说话吗？
Are you talking to me?
没有呀
No.
姐姐 我可不可以吻你一下？
May I kiss you?
笑什么？
Why are you smiling?
笑？我没什么呀
Am I? It's nothing.
青田化工
Go down!
下来…
Stand on one side!
下来
-Stand together! Quickly! -Quickly!
那么糟糕！阿刘 他们是什么人呀？
Gosh! Who are they, Lau?
有三个持械行劫的积犯
Three armed robbers with criminal records
刚打劫了解款车
just robbed a cash escort car
被我们的兄弟追到化工厂这里来
and were chased here by our men.
里面有八个人质
There are eight hostages inside
两个是解款车司机及守卫
including drivers and guards.
现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
我们现在迫他们出来
We will force them out.
给我一件
Give me one!
准备
Get ready!
放
Fire!
不用怕 是催泪弹而已 戴口罩
-Calm down, it's tear gas. Wear masks! -Wear masks!
出去
Get out!
去你的！出去
Damn! Get out!
枪呀
Quickly!
不准开枪
Give me the revolver!
你们全都听着
-Don't fire! -Listen up!
除了她外 里面还有很多人质
There are many more hostages inside!
限你两小时内给我们一架直升机离去
Get me a helicopter in two hours
不然我每五分钟杀一个人
or I'll kill one hostage every five minutes!
各位阿Sir 各位早安
Hello, sirs!
她是谁？
Who is she?
职业枪手陈七呀
A professional gunner, Chan Chat.
阿Sir 别这样子说我嘛
Sir, don't call me that.
我只杀该死的贱人而已
I only kill those who deserve to die.
你叫我捕头吧
Call me Thief Catcher.
我们警方不会花钱请你这种人的
The police won't hire you.
花钱？
Hire?
阿Sir 这次我吃亏点 便宜你
Sir, I'll do you a favor this time.
是免费的
It's free of charge.
抓住他
-Get them! -Yes, sir!
我投降了别开枪呀
I surrender! Don't fire! I surrender! Don't…
我投降了！不要…
Rescue the hostages! -Rescue the hostages. -Let's go.
快去救人质
-Rescue the hostages. -Come on!
伏下…
Lie down!
进去看还有没有人
Go and see if there are still hostages inside!
我结了婚的
I'm married.
去
So?
看来这事
It seems like
只有我才有本事替你找回儿子
only I can get your son back.
找回来是活生生的 收五十万
Pay me 500,000 if he's alive
死了你也不嫌弃 收十五万
and 150,000 if you don't mind he's dead.
我只收黄金 我的电话号码呀
I only take gold. Here's my number.
考虑清楚便打电话给我吧
Call me after you've thought about it.
报馆被人利用了
The newspaper has been used.
登报纸的根本不是来抓婴儿的
The one who placed the advertisement is
叫兄弟们们小心看着
not here for the babies. Warn the others.
是 刘Sir
Yes, sir.
刘太 你可以过去
Mrs. Lau, you may go.
请给我看看证件
Please show me your pass.
你今晚来干什么
What brings you here tonight?
我答应过护士长
I promised the head nurse
每星期一三五都来帮忙
to come and help every alternate day.
上面的老婆婆…
The old lady up there--
要见到你才肯做物理治疗！对吗？
Won't do physiotherapy without you.
你知就好了
So you know that already.
我要照顾那么多东西
I'm busy.
只怕照顾不了你呀
I can't take care of you.
小心点
Stay safe.
你也是
You too.
你就是登报纸的那个人？
Are you the one who placed the advertisement?
你是不是警察？
Are you a cop?
告诉你 我今天晚上要杀掉所有婴儿
Listen. I'm going to kill all the babies tonight.
你干什么？
What are you doing?
不要…
No!
别过来 不然我杀了她
Don't move or I'll kill her!
你别乱来
Calm down.
放下！把那枝东西放下
Drop that!
不然我杀了她
Or I'll kill her!
你先放下
Drop that knife first!
我会杀了她的
I'll kill her!
好！我放
Okay! I'm dropping it!
进去里面呀
Go inside!
不然我杀了她
I'll kill her!
进去
Go inside!
他们把我儿子医死了
Those doctors killed my son.
我要那些婴儿陪葬
This is my revenge!
我要把婴儿杀光
-I'll kill all those babies! -Dr. Wong.
黄医生请到急诊室
Please hurry to the emergency ward.
Dr. Wong, please hurry to the emergency--
我要把婴儿杀光
I'll kill all the babies!
你流血了！抹了它
You're bleeding! Wipe it off.
我没事
I'm fine.
你猜我们能可否撞开呢？
Hey. Do you think we can break down the door?
没可能！这门那么厚
No way, it's too thick.
让我试试
Let me try.
那锁匙就在外面
The keys are just outside.
差一点点便可以摸到了
Just a bit more and I could get them!
你不用那么紧张呀
Calm down.
那疯子没那么快回来的
The madman won't be back so soon.
我担心那些小孩子而已
I'm only worried about the babies.
你没听到那疯子刚才说什么吗？
Didn't you hear what he said just now?
让我来
Let me try.
你还不走？
Why aren't you leaving?
收到了！你别紧张 慢慢说
Roger that.
只有一个人而已？
Stay calm, speak slowly.
是呀
-Just one person? -Yes!
这么迟！你新来的吗？
You are late! Are you new here?
带他出去
Take him out.
是
-Yes, sir! -Yes, sir!
别动！起来
Don't move! Get up!
我要把婴儿杀光…
-I'll kill all the babies! -Move!
老公
Dear! Dear?
我已经把那疯子制服了
I have captured the madman.
我知道
I know.
幸亏你及时通知我
Thank you for informing me on time.
我没有白来吧
I didn't come here for nothing.
走呀
Come here.
有没有奖品？
Any rewards?
没有
No!
老婆婆在上面等你呀 还不上去？
Don't keep the old lady waiting.
已经搅定了
It's done already.
你真顽皮！掩着嘴巴笑我？
Naughty! Are you laughing at me?
要不要等你一起走？
Are you leaving with me?
不用了！主角还没出场
No. The real one hasn't turned up yet.
什么？
What?
惊奇什么？
Why are you surprised?
你那么好管闲事！带你出去兜兜风
You're nosy. Let's go for a ride.
走了
Let's go!
刘Sir 有人偷婴儿呀
Officer Lau, someone is kidnapping a baby.
不要开枪 那婴儿可能在里面的
Don't shoot! The baby might be in there!
各位兄弟 不准开枪
Attention. Don't fire! Don't fire!
走了
I'm leaving!
追
-Go after her! -Go after her!
女捕头？!
The Thief Catcher?
小三八 怎么张开了小嘴巴？
Hey, Nosy. What's with your mouth?
别睡呀 好戏还在后头
Don't sleep. More fun is coming.
这次好玩吗？
Isn't it fun?
还引不到你？追来吧
There you are. Follow me!
先睡一下
Let's take a rest first.
不是吧？这样也跟不到我？
I can't believe you still can't get me.
怎出来混呀？
What a shame.
无声无息这么阴险
Not even a noise? That's sinister!
原来是个女人
So you're a woman!
原来是个婆娘
So you're a bitch!
告诉我 你为什么偷那么多婴儿？
Why did you kidnap all those babies?
你够了吧？干嘛掉转来说我…
What? You're blaming me for that?
看你站得那么刁钻…
You look pretty smart.
难道你就是那个女黑侠？
Are you that Wonder Woman?
你就是那个女捕头？
Are you the Thief Catcher?
知道的你便别碍着我发财
Don't get in my way then!
为了花红 你竟用婴儿做饵
How could you use a baby
引他们出来？
as your bait?
太卑鄙了
How despicable!
你够了吧
That's enough!
先把婴儿放下
Put the baby down first.
好！看你有没有本事
Let's see if you can make me do that!
刚才是热身 现在来真的
That was just a warm-up. Now, it's the real thing!
等一等…
Hey, wait!
搅什么鬼？
What's happening?
隐形人？
Invisible Woman?
多了一个人？
There's one more person here?
那个人好像是来帮我的
She seems to be on my side.
婴儿？
The baby!
小心呀
Be careful!
那婴儿怎么了？
How's the baby? Hey!
等一等 你是谁呀？
Wait, who are you? Hey!
没事 没事了！乖呀
Everything's fine now.
够了吧 佛也会发火的
All right, don't test my patience!
你是谁？
Who are you?
陈七 走吧
Let's go, Chan Chat!
陈三 是你呀？
Chan Sum? It's you?
走吧
Let's go!
别拉我 我自己走 不要呀
Don't pull me! I can walk on my own!
局长 我怀疑今晚的事
Chief, I suspect the Thief Catcher you hired is the one
是你聘请的女捕头做
behind this incident today.
你怎知道的？
How do you know?
你叫她立刻把婴儿交回医院吧
Ask her to bring the baby back at once.
叫医生
Call the doctor.
那婴儿怎么了？
How's the baby?
把他救回
Save him.
你放心
You can count on me.
推进急诊室去
To the emergency ward!
医生 怎么了？
Doctor, how's the baby?
对不起 太迟！救不到了
I'm sorry, it's too late. I couldn't save him.
通知他的家人
Call his parents.
知道了 刘Sir
Yes, sir.
青青 你别走呀
Ching-ching, don't go!
师父不会喜欢一个那么窝囊的徒儿
Our master hates idiots like me.
我舍不得你呀
I'll miss you.
你自己照顾自己吧
Take care of yourself.
别哭
Don't cry.
青青
Ching-ching!
不许追
Let her go!
跪下
Kneel down.
东东你留在这里
Tung-tung. You must stay here
是要把我要你和师姐完成的使命
and fulfill the fate you and your martial sister
独力承担
shared alone.
将来为师父行侠仗义的责任
You're going to uphold justice for me
就由你一人承担
on your own.
东东 你干嘛哭呀？
Tung-tung, why are you crying?
我没有
No, I'm not.
到底为什么？
Tell me why.
真的没什么
It's nothing.
今天医院那案子怎么了？
How's the case today?
那失踪的婴儿 跌死了
The missing baby fell to his death.
十多年没见 你身手还挺好的
It has been ten years. You're still great.
那只老怪物从那里拿到那隐形衣？
Where did that monster get an invisible robe?
婴儿这事也是他策动的
He's behind all this.
你还会插手吗？
Are you going to interfere?
谢谢你了
No, thank you.
当年在那地洞跑出来
When I escaped from that cave,
多亏你捉到我也不杀我
you spared me even though you've already caught me.
现我很珍惜自己
Now I'm taking good care of myself.
那老怪物把那么多婴儿子抓走干嘛？
What does he want so many babies for?
等下次日全蚀 选其中一个做皇帝
He'll choose one to be the emperor in the next eclipse.
当不到皇帝的
And the rest
就像你我一样 做他的杀手吗？
will become his killers like us?
不止 公公会把他们变成陈九
Moreover, Master would even turn them into Chan Gau.
陈三 不如你行行好
Chan Sum, do them a favor.
把婴儿们杀掉好了
Just kill the babies.
我被那怪物毒了三年
That monster has corrupted me for three years.
那次逃跑出来后
After I had escaped,
我花了十年时间
I've spent ten years
才能把自己当回一个人
to return to normal!
我不想那些婴儿全变成怪物
I don't want the babies to become monsters.
你可当作全不知情
Just pretend that you know nothing
别再插手
and leave them alone.
不然公公命令一下
If Master gives the order,
我一样会杀你
I'd kill you as well.
要杀的现在杀
Do it then!
下次你躲不了
You won't be so lucky next time!
全告知我 我能当什么也不知吗？
Now that you've told me everything, how can I feign ignorance?
你不再是青青
You won't be called Ching-ching anymore.
从今天开始 你叫陈三
From now on, you are Chan Sum!
隐形衣十日之内务必要到手
You must get the invisible robe in ten days
事成之后 将博士杀之
and kill the professor after that.
若有失责 死路一条
Do it or you'll die.
（复制）
Hey, what are you doing?
你干什么？
I've told you many times.
我说过多次 这里很危险的 出去吧
It's dangerous here. Leave, please!
什么危险？你日夜在这儿都没事
What's so dangerous? You're always here.
你总是不让我进来 你有什么隐瞒我
Are you keeping something from me?
你有什么不知道的？
You already know everything.
你说隐形衣我也有份
You said the robe is mine too,
怎么隐形衣能见紫外光 我却不知道
but I didn't know it can stand UV light.
隐形衣还不能见紫外光
No, it still can't.
如果可以 你一定是第一个知道
You'll be the first one to know if it can.
那么这几天你在研究些什么？
What have you been working on these past few days then?
我在研究这个急诊室
I'm working on this Revival Box.
本来已经死掉
These were dead before,
但现在全部都救活了
but they are alive again.
有没有花的？
Do they have any flowers?
有！一个月之后便有了
Yes. They will bloom in a month.
心靖
Sum-ching.
你可以每天替我拿出去晒太阳吗？
Will you put them under the sun every day
晚上浇浇水
and water them at night?
幸运星 是你教我折的
You taught me how to make these lucky stars.
你一定会见到花开的
You'll see them bloom.
十日内务必要将隐形衣到手
You must get the invisible robe in ten days
事成之后将博士杀之
and kill the professor after that.
如有失责 死路一条
Do it or you'll die.
你下属很嚣张啊！关我两个多小时
Hey! Your men kept me for over two hours!
这的确不关我事 是意外嘛
Don't blame me. It was an accident!
意外？
Accident?
如果不是你 那婴儿怎会死？
The baby died because of you!
你说什么呀？
What?
是我推他下去吗？
I didn't drop him!
女飞侠窝囊救不到他而已
It's Wonder Woman's fault that she couldn't save him!
现在你可以走
You may go now,
不过 你骗到所有人骗不了你自己
but you can't deceive yourself.
够了吧！这个黑锅分明是你要我背的
Hey! Enough!
好 算我吃亏点 我尽管替你瞄一瞄
Stop making me the scapegoat!
姑娘 最重要是看看我的儿子
Fine, it's my loss. I'll keep an eye on it.
放心 我收你钱一定替你服务
Keep an extra eye on my son, miss.
谢谢
-Don't worry, I'll help my client. -Thank you!
这次真是自讨苦吃
I'm just asking for trouble!
搅定
Done.
搅什么鬼呀！那么多鸟笼
Why are there so many birdcages?
糟糕！惊动了老怪物
This is bad! That monster is here!
喂！喂
Hey! Hey!
怎么还是中招了
I still got hit!
看你熬得多久
Let's see how long you can stand it.
闯入魔宫的女人 你知是什么人吗？
Do you know who the intruder was?
不知道
No.
我想起了一个人
I have someone in mind,
不过她应在十年前死了
but she should have died ten years ago.
对
Yes.
陈七是我亲手杀死
I killed Chan Chat myself.
能够单枪匹马闯进来的 只有女飞侠
Now, only Wonder Woman could get in by herself.
她一直都插手失踪婴儿的事
She has been meddling with our plan.
最有可能是她
She's probably the intruder.
公公 让我杀了她
Let me kill her, Master.
这些东西有别的人去做
Leave it to the others.
阿九
Chan Gau.
替我杀了她 必要的时候
Kill the woman. And if necessary,
跟她同归于尽
die with her.
你这只死老怪物
You damned monster.
无论如何我也不能让金针进脑
I won't let the needles go up to my head.
我们现已经证实
We proved that this case is unrelated
这件事与以往的无关
to the previous incidents.
我们已向市长保证
We promised the mayor
以后不会有同样事情发生
it wouldn't happen again.
你的订金呀
Here's your deposit!
什么订金呀？
What deposit?
你儿子失踪那事我不干了
I'm not pursuing your son's case!
我现在开会 迟些再谈
Hey! We'll talk later. I'm in a meeting.
不行
No!
不用再商量了
The deal is off!
小姐 你一定是调查到些什么
Miss. You must have gotten hold of something.
为了十多个婴儿生命 请你说出来
Please tell us for the babies' sake.
告诉你有个屁用？!
What good would it do to me?
你们要是有用便不用聘请我啦
You won't hire me if you can handle it.
为了正义 你应该…
For justice, you should--
正你妈的
You must have gotten hold of something.
为了正义 我命都没有了
I almost got killed!
你把孩子害死了
You killed the baby!
把你知道的告诉我
Tell me what you know.
你以为我会理你吗？
Do you think I'd listen to you?
你会
You will.
刚才那娃娃掉下来的时候
When that baby is falling down,
你想也不想就伸手去接
you saved it without a second thought.
是！那个婴儿是我杀死的
Yes, I killed the baby.
现在我也快死了
But I'm dying too.
就这样算了吧？行不行呀？
We are even now!
你还不肯放过我？
Won't you leave me alone?
我只想找个地方静静躲起来死而已
I only want to die in peace!
我只想知道谁偷了婴儿
I want to know who took the babies.
别对付那隐形人
Don't hurt the Invisible Woman!
她只不过是个身不由己的小角色
She's only a puppet.
死老怪物
That damned monster!
我死都不让毒针上我脑
I won't let his needles kill me.
不要
Don't do that!
趁我还有理智之前 你快走
Go away before I lose my mind.
我不走
I'm not leaving.
你会死的
You'll die!
死也要死得有价值
It's fine to die for a good reason.
我只可把你体内的毒针暂时封着
I can stop the needles from going further,
但拿不出来
but I can't get them out.
好！我利用这段时间
Okay, I'll use the time you bought me
帮你从公公处取回婴儿
to get the babies back.
如果我们要稳操胜券
If we succeed,
一定要拖陈三下水
we must get Chan Sum to help us.
隐形人？
The Invisible Woman?
对！在我未找到陈三之前
Yes. Before I find her, we must be careful.
我们必须小心点
That monster discovered me
上次闯入魔宫 我惊动了那老怪物
when I sneaked into his cave last time.
他以为那个是你
He thought it was you.
他现在派了陈九来对付你
So he is sending Chan Gau to kill you now.
一个来历不明的神经汉
Officer Lau, a madman is holding hostage
挟持了几十人在车站内
dozens of people in the station
还破坏了车站的电脑系统
and destroyed the station's computer system.
现在有一班载货的列车
A cargo train is charging
正冲向火车站呀
toward the station now.
还有多久火车便撞上火车站？
When will it hit the station?
大概五分钟
In about five minutes.
知道
Got it.
所有单位准备
All units, get ready!
小心地雷
Be careful of the land mines!
别踩下去
Don't step on them!
别动
Don't move!
大家小心 有地雷呀
Be careful! There are land mines!
快进去呀
Watch out! Go now!
还有一分钟火车便撞上车站
The train will crash in one minute.
进去
Go in there!
先救里面的人质
Save the hostages inside first.
还不进去？
Why aren't you going in?
走呀
Run!
小心！快撞上了
Brace yourself!
让我来
Leave it to me!
快走呀
Run!
站长 怎样才可把车子弄停呀？
Sir, how can we stop the train?
那电脑系统被那神经汉弄坏了
The madman has destroyed the computer!
不能停了！走吧
It can't be stopped. Go quickly!
走呀 火车撞进来了
Run! The train is here!
接住
Take it!
快走
Let's go!
老公
Dear.
医生怎么说？
What did the doctor say?
医生说 幸运的半年便可以走路了
If you're lucky, you can walk in six months.
不幸的呢？
Otherwise?
如果不幸的话…
Otherwise,
可能会残废
you may become a cripple.
别这样子
Cheer up.
能做女飞侠的老公
As Wonder Woman's husband,
我会支持你每个决定
I'll always stand by you.
你什么时候知道？
When did you find out?
在车站门口
At the station,
你看着我 不想进去的时候
when you looked at me, unwilling to go in.
以后不许偷偷笑
No more secret smiles from now on
也不许躲起来掉眼泪
and no more secret tears.
有什么事要告诉我
Just tell me everything.
好不好？
Okay?
老公
Dear.
有花蕾了
Hey! There's a flower bud--
你干么？先坐下吧
What's wrong? Sit down first.
不行 我刚想到些头绪
No, I just got a clue.
我要赶快写下来
I must write it down now!
你先坐下吧
Sit down first.
你快点出去
Leave now!
你知道了多久？
How long have you known about it?
我一直都知道
I've always known about it.
在研究的过程中
In the process,
我发现隐形衣放出一些毒素
I found that the invisible robe emits toxins.
所以我一直都不让你留在这里
That's why I always tell you to stay out of here.
但是素心兰已经有花蕾
But a flower bud has grown.
既然花也能救活 我也不会有事
I'll be okay if the flowers can be saved.
你快点走吧
Come on, get out of here.
我们是拍档 你这样子 我怎能离开
We are partners. How can I leave you like this?
我的眼镜呢？
Where are my glasses?
你戴着
You're wearing them.
那隐形衣还未完成…
Before the robe is finished,
我是不会死的
I will not die.
我还可以嗅到你头发的香味
I can still smell the fragrance in your hair.
（别哭）
不如带我出去看看那些花吧？
Let's look at the flowers outside.
我没事的
I'll be fine.
你出去
Get out of here!
放我进来呀
Let me in!
就算你能进来 我也不会出去的
I won't go out even if you can get in.
那件隐形衣会在素心兰开花时完成
The robe will be ready when the flowers bloom.
你答应我会照顾到它们开花的
You promised to take care of them until then.
你忘记了吗？
Have you forgotten about that?
陈三
Chan Sum.
你为什么还要去见那个老怪物？
Why are you still meeting that monster?
你这样隐瞒 他会放过李之博士吗？
He won't let the professor live anyway.
那隐形衣成功了 他一样要你杀了他
He'll kill him once the robe is finished!
你中了多少针？
How many needles were you attacked with?
只要你肯帮忙
If you help us,
我跟女飞侠都有机会干掉他
Wonder Woman and I may stand a chance to kill him.
这么怕死
If you fear death so much,
都不知道为什么你要去帮女飞侠
how can you help Wonder Woman?
无论你怎么说 我也不会谢谢你的
I won't thank you.
我的命是你捡回来的
You saved my life.
但你问你自己 为了保护博士
But to protect the professor,
你宁愿被老怪物控制
you let that monster control you.
你害了多少无辜的婴儿？
You have harmed so many babies.
你骗到别人 骗不到你自己
You can deceive others but not yourself.
现女飞侠可以帮你
Wonder Woman can help you now.
明天我会在你放走我的那个地方等你
I'll see you at the same spot tomorrow.
见不到你 我不会走
I'll wait until you come!
你千万要来啊
You'd better come.
我没时间再等了 请你快一点
I don't have time. Please hurry.
成功了
I did it!
心靖…心靖
Sum-ching! Sum-ching!
幸运星
Lucky star.
心靖 隐形衣终于成功了
Sum-ching, the invisible robe is finally finished.
为什么隐形衣还未到手？
Why haven't you gotten that robe?
因为隐形衣倘不能在日光下发挥作用
It can't work under the sun yet.
皇上军队的威力便会大减
The strength of the Emperor's army will be reduced.
而方程式已经接近完成阶段
It'll soon be finished.
我想 多给博士几天
Give the professor a few more days.
明天日落前 成功与否
Get it no matter what
也要把隐形衣拿到手
before sunset tomorrow.
到时 阿九会帮你
Chan Gau will help you then.
在公公的大计内 我陈三所做的事
Master, all my work in your great plan
算得了什么？
are inconsequential.
只要我在这些储君内找到真命天子
If I find an emperor among those babies,
你便是个大功臣
you'll be honored for your services.
所有储君都应该休息
All princes should be asleep.
你不该不去睡
You should go to sleep too.
九月十八日
September 18th.
今天…
Today,
我终于发现了
I've finally solved the UV light problem.
隐形衣克服紫外光的方程式
But I've also reached the end of my life too.
可惜也是到了我死的时候
From the first day when I started working on the invisible robe,
由研究隐形衣的第一天
I knew I would die from the toxins.
我已经知道自己会中毒而死
Without Sum-ching,
如果没有心靖的存在
I wouldn't have been able to face it.
我根本没有勇气去面对
If she knows that my only hope now
要是她知道我现在唯一的希望
is to take her hands
只是想捉着她的手
and witness the flowers bloom,
一起看素心兰开花
will she still kill me?
不知道…她还会不会杀我？
The day has come.
黄道吉日已到 无论隐形衣成功与否
Regardless of the progress,
都要把它拿回来
get the invisible robe
然后 把博士处死
and kill the professor.
博士 我以后都不会再回来的了
Professor, I'll never return to you.
见不到你 我是不会离开的
I won't leave until I see you.
相信我
Believe me.
你现在的处境非常危险
You are in great danger.
尽快离开实验室吧
Leave the lab now.
真笨
Damn it!
连女飞侠都迟到
Even Wonder Woman is late.
笨蛋！早知道不约什么不见不散
I shouldn't have promised to come.
都不知道该不该走
Should I leave or not?
你还真赏脸
Great. There you are.
是公公叫我来杀你的
Master sent me to kill you.
慢点 陈三
Wait, Chan Sum.
动手吧 这次我不会放过你的
I won't let you go this time.
你以为你能忍心下手吗？
Can you really do it?
公公的命令我一定要执行
I must execute Master's order.
但我可以答应你
But I can promise you
你死了之后我可以帮你做一件事
that I'll do you a favor after you die.
曼着！现在死的未必是我
Wait, it might be you who'll die.
也许是你
有什么未做完的事情
我可以帮你 你说吧
Tell me your last wish. Tell me!
那么帮我照顾博士吧
Take care of the professor.
博士？
The professor?
替我去救博士
Save the professor for me.
陈三 你干什么？
Chan Sum, what are you doing?
她不是来杀人
She didn't come to kill you.
她是来自杀
She came to kill herself.
你不要自己的命来救那个家伙？
You are giving up your life to save him?
自己的命？
My life?
我只不过是公公一只杀人野兽而已
I am just Master's killing machine.
野兽是不会有感情的
A machine won't have feelings
更加不会为了另一个人牺牲自己
or sacrifice themselves for someone.
你肯面对自己
Life is meaningful
你的生命比死更有意义
if you can face yourself.
我就是不能够面对自己
Not just myself,
更加不能面对他
but I can't even face him!
陈三…
Chan Sum!
这样便走光了？
So you're all leaving?
碰碰你也走开？!
Damn, can't you stay put?
还是骑自己的铁马比较听话
My own bike is better.
等等我呀
Wait for me!
陈三
Chan Sum!
你可以由现在开始改变的
You can change yourself from now on!
那又如何？我不一样是陈三？
So what? I'm still Chan Sum!
陈三又如何？可以变陈七嘛
You can be another Chan Chat!
太迟了！你们别跟着我 让我来
It's too late! Leave me alone!
真讨厌！铁马也不够真马跑得快？!
Shit! Even a bike can't catch up?
去
Go!
你能够逃避你以前做的事
You've shunned your past.
这分钟才是你的真本性
This is your true self!
那么我更加该死
I shouldn't live then!
不要
No!
糟糕
This is bad!
你两个闯了个祸出来了
You two are in great trouble!
命大 撑着吧
So lucky. Brace yourselves!
东东？
Tung-tung?
青青？
Ching-ching?
你放手 不然会一起掉下去
Let go of my hand or we'll both fall!
不放
No!
接住呀
Grab it!
我撑不住了！撑不住了
I can't hold on any longer!
我不会放手的
I won't let go!
要放一起放
We must be together.
真的是你
It's really you.
你两个认识的吗？
You two knew each other?
我忘记了
I don't remember.
以前的东西不重要
The past is trivial.
最重要是你现在心里面想做些什么
What matters is the thing you wish to do now.
你想做什么便说嘛
Hey! What do you want to do?
公公派了陈九去杀博士
Master sent Chan Gau to kill the professor.
我要回去救他
I want to save him.
博士？!
The professor?
拿来
Give it to me.
隐形衣已经可以见紫外光
The invisible robe can withstand UV light now.
没有人可以找到它
Nobody can find it.
不要呀
No!
心靖我还有很多事对你说
Sum-ching. I have so much to tell you.
全在那份礼物里
It's all inside the gift box.
你怎么打他也没用
It doesn't matter how hard you hit him.
他拿不到他要的 他绝对不会放手
He'll stick to what he wants.
不行！你不可以给他的
No! You can't give it to him.
我现在什么都没有
I have lost everything.
我不可以让他死
I can't let him die.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我知道公公是不能令你杀我的
I knew Master can't make you kill me.
拿得这么容易？
It won't be that easy!
慢着 等一等…
Wait, hold on!
小白痴 声带在这儿
Idiot, here's the tape.
过来拿吧！快来拿走
Come and get it!
再见了
Goodbye!
炉太热了 不能再留在这里
It's too hot here!
心靖 仪器毁灭了
Sum-ching, it's better to have it destroyed
总好过落在他手里
than to let him have it.
走吧
Hey! Let's go!
你们走吧
Go ahead.
那么你…
What about-
由她去
Let her be.
去哪里呀？
Where are we going?
我们去魔宫救婴儿
To save the babies from the cave.
只我们两个？让我回去拿点家伙
Just the two of us? Let me get my stuff first.
可否让我看看开了花的素心兰？
May I look at the blooming flowers?
所有婴儿都放在这里
All the babies are here.
但切勿触动任何东西
Don't touch anything.
如果在这儿开杀戒 婴儿们都会没命
The babies will die if we fight here.
死老怪物 快来受死
You damned monster, come on and die!
这里很重沼气 小心中毒
Beware. This place is full of methane.
你这死老怪物 沼气当氧气
You damned monster like methane more than oxygen.
我宰了你
I'll kill you.
你两个胆敢闯进我禁宫？
How dare you come here!
揍她
Attack her!
特异功能？
Special powers?
你现在才来跪他？
You are kneeling to him now? Weren't you bold before?
你的骨气那里去了？
I can't help it.
我不是跪他
My legs feel like jelly.
我是腿软呀
Do you think someone like you can beat me?
就凭你两个就想以下犯上
It's no use kneeling to me. Guards, go!
你跪我也没用了 四大护法
-Yes! -Yes!
反正都是死路一条
We have no way out now.
你对付公公 我去对付那四个
Deal with Master, I'll handle the others.
冲呀
Go!
能够死在我手上 是你的光荣
It's an honor to die by my hands.
糟了 不知是否多吸了沼气 很兴奋
Damn it. I think I'm high on methane.
怎么办？一定不是他的对手
What should we do? We can't beat him.
别让他集中精神 上
Don't let him concentrate. Go!
这次我要取你们的命
I'll kill you this time.
东东 快带陈七走
Tung-tung, go with Chan Chat!
不行 我要跟她拼命
No, I'll fight until the end!
不要
No!
你们再不走 便会中毒
You'll be poisoned if you stay.
撑不住了 先吸点氧气
Let's go!
去你的！你们去死吧
I'll need some oxygen.
好了！这次还不连你的毛都炸掉？!
Go to hell, all of you!
怎么这个迟得那么厉害？
He must have been blown up to pieces this time.
他还没有死
Why is this one so late? He's still alive!
炸死你
Damn you!
他怕光的
He's afraid of lights.
再多掷几个
Give me some more.
糟了？我的脸有没有事呀？
Is my face still pretty?
干什么…
What?
我不知道你死了没有
I don't know if you're fine or not,
我却被你吓死了
but you scared me to death!
他还没有死？
He's still alive?
他还会动
How is this possible?
他的肉身虽毁了
We destroyed his body,
但他的意志还能控制自己
but his mind is still there.
他控制住我
He has gained control over me!
我来帮你
Let me help you.
别过来呀
Don't come near me!
我控制不了自己
I can't control myself!
快走！走呀
Go. Quick!
带陈七走呀
Go with Chan Chat!
怎办？
What should we do?
走
Go!
青青
Ching-ching!
别让我再打
Don't let me do it again!
你妈的
Fuck you!
你死吧你…
Die!
走呀
Go!
去你的白骨精
You son of a bitch!
他上了我身 快离开这里
He's controlling my body, go!
要死 就大家一起死
We won't leave you behind!
我重见你已很开心的了
I'm happy to have met you again!
对不起呀
I'm sorry!
陈三
Chan Sum!
- 陈三 - 青青
-Chan Sum! -Ching-ching!
老怪物 一起死吧
I'll die with you, damned monster!
中国是不可以没皇帝的…
China must have an emperor.
以前的不重要 最重要是现在
中国是不可没皇帝的
What's important is today, not the past.
可否跟我一起看素心兰开花？
Can we see the blooming flowers together?
博士
Professor!
青青
Ching-ching.
你不会死的
You won't die.
老老实实 你们在地面才说吧
Hey! Get on the ground before you talk.
不然我会死的
Otherwise, I'll die!
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
陈七呢？
Where's Chan Chat?
有好东西…
I got something good!
来一件吧 不然一会有记者来拍照
Take one, or when the press comes,
我们这样子很不体面嘛
we'll look shabby!
来 披上它吧
Come on, put them on!
轰动一时的婴儿失踪案
The police have solved
已被警方瓦解了
the missing babies case.
大部分失踪婴儿已寻回
Most of the missing babies have been found.
以下是本台记者现场报导
Here's our live report.
传闻此案是由
We heard that
三位来历不明的女侠所侦破
three unknown heroines solved it.
不知道他们跟警方有什么关系呢？
How are they related to the police?
没密切的关系 他们是警方的朋友
They are close friends of the police.
那么他们三位是什么身份？
Who are they?
无可奉告
No comment.
那么你知不知她们什么时候再出现呢
When will they come again?
有需要的话他们便会出现
When we need them.
那么你知不知道她们叫什么名字？
Do you know their names?
叫什么名字？
-Their names? -Yes, their names.
她们叫“东方三侠“
They are called The Heroic Trio.
我们什么时候起了这个名字
-The Heroic Trio? -The Heroic Trio?
你怎会知道她们的名字？
When did we get that name?
这名字是怎来的？
-How do you know that?
这是警方的高度秘密 对不起…
-Where does the name come from? -It's top-secret, I'm sorry.
随便说一个而已
I was just improvising it a bit.
谁和谁和谁之间
相识结合了患难
情和情和情的关
辗转里掠过站和站
一曲一折只是我
一转身某一天某一刻的事
一举一动都只是
闲事难事然后变传奇事
人和人和人之间
沧桑里自有浪漫
日复夜复日之间
崎岖夹杂了梦幻
一曲一折只是我
一转身某一天某一刻的事
一举一动都只是
闲事难事然后变传奇事
莫问当初我哀我乐我陪着我
步步惊心我走我的路
莫问今天对天对地我仍是我
在是是非非里举步
莫问他朝到底有没有谁像我
任动地惊天放声笑傲
莫问一生有风有月有谁伴我
在大地不必各走各路
人和人和人之间
沧桑里自有浪漫
日复夜复日之间
崎岖夹杂了梦幻
一曲一折只是我
一转身某一天某一刻的事
一举一动都只是
闲事难事然后变传奇事